<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_1921">
		<text>Thompson Model 1921</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_1921_s">
		<text>Thompson M1921</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_1921_descr">
		<text>The Thompson is a blowback-operated, air-cooled, magazine-fed selective-fire submachine gun, invented and developed by John T. Thompson in 1918 to break the stalemate of trench warfare of World War I. It became notorious during the Prohibition era as the signature weapon of various organized crime syndicates in the United States in the 1920s, before being widely used by the Allies during World War II.\n
		The M1921 was the the first major production model, nicknamed the "Chicago Typewriter", and expensive to manufacture. It features a faster firerate and the Blish Lock system for weapon operation.</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_thompson_1928">
		<text>Thompson Model 1928</text>
	</string>
    <string id="st_wpn_thompson_1928_s">
		<text>Thompson M1928</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_1928_descr">
		<text>The M1928 was the first variant of the Thompson produced primarily for military use. The original samples were Model 1921s with weight added to the actuator, which slowed down the cyclic rate of fire as required by the Navy. A front grip and muzzle device were also mounted by default.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_m1a1">
		<text>Thompson M1A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_thompson_m1a1_descr">
		<text>The M1A1 is a variant of the M1, a simplified Thompson model intended for the military that removed the front grip, muzzle device, and the ability to use drum magazines, and reduced the fire rate. The M1A1 was itself further simplified, with further changes, like the firing pin being machined to the face of the bolt, eliminating unnecessary parts. While this reduced the cost of the weapon to a third and eventually a fourth of the original M1921, the M1A1 had its fire rate further reduced.</text>
	</string>



	<string id="st_up_m1a1_b8_name">
		<text>Installation of a heavier barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_m1a1_b8_descr">
		<text>Installation of a heavier barrel to improve recoil further</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_m1a1_b5_name">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Stock</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_m1a1_b5_descr">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Stock to replace the wooden parts for a quick weight reduction.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_m1a1_b6_name">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Handguard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_m1a1_b6_descr">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Handguard to replace the wooden parts for a slight weight reduction.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_up_m1a1_b7_name">
		<text>Installation of Anti-Corrosive Parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b7_descr">
		<text>Installation of weapon components that take a harder time to degrade.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_1921_b8_name">
		<text>Installation of High Quality Imported Parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b8_descr">
		<text>Installation of higher quality parts imported from the USA to increase the reliability of the gun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b5_name">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Stock</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b5_descr">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Stock to replace the wooden parts for a quick weight reduction.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b6_name">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Handguard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b6_descr">
		<text>Installation of Polymer Handguard to replace the wooden parts for a slight weight reduction.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="st_up_1921_b7_name">
		<text>Installation of Anti-Corrosive Parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b7_descr">
		<text>Installation of weapon components that take a harder time to degrade.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_1921_b9_name">
		<text>Installation of Re-engineered Blish Lock Mechanism</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_1921_b9_descr">
		<text>Installation of a tweaked locking mechanism to greatly enhance the reliability of the gun.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_mag_m1a1_11.43x23_fmj">
		<text>Standard Thompson Stick Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_m1a1_11.43x23_fmj_descr">
		<text>30-round magazine for the M1A1, chambered in .45 ACP.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Will fit the 1921 variant as well.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_1921_11.43x23_fmj">
		<text>Standard Thompson Drum Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_1921_11.43x23_fmj_descr">
		<text>50-round drum magazine used for the models 1921 and 1928 of the Thompson, chambered in .45 ACP.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Will not fit M1A1 variant, as its magwell is different.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_1921_11.43x23_extended">
		<text>Extended Thompson Drum Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_1921_11.43x23_extended_descr">
		<text>100-round Drum magazine used for the models 1921 and 1928 of the Thompson, chambered in .45 ACP.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Will not fit M1A1 variant, as its magwell is different.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>