<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_kedr">
		<text>PP-91-01 "Kedr-B"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_kedr_descr">
		<text>The Kedr submachine gun was developed in the early 1990s based on the experimental PP-71 designed by E. F. Dragunov, created in the 1970s for the Soviet Army. Since 1993, a new model designated Kedr (designed by Evgeny Dragunov) went into serial production and was primarily intended to arm special police units and internal troops of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of the Russian Federation. Based on the basic model, designers at the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant developed the PP-91-01 Kedr-B submachine gun with an integrated silencer. The silencer can be removed for ease of carrying.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: 9mm suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis_saw">
		<text>OTs-02 Kiparis "Saw"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis_saw_descr">
		<text>A special modification for the southern frontiers of Duty. Ideal for clearing areas of packs of small mutants and engaging lightly armored enemies.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon is equipped with: a Picatinny rail for small-sized optics, a tactical foregrip, and a laser designator. Comes with multiple 50-round drum magazines.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Trijicon Acog and Red Dot Sights for Picatinny
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: 9mm suppressor (The package includes a thermal case for the suppressor)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_kiparis_9x18_drum_50">
		<text>50-round 9x18 Kiparis Drum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_kiparis_9x18_drum_50_descr">
		<text>
		Drum 9x18 Kiparis Magazine with a capacity of 50 rounds.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_kiparis_9x19_drum_50">
		<text>50-round 9x19 Kiparis Drum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_kiparis_9x19_drum_50_descr">
		<text>
		Drum 9x19 Kiparis Magazine with a capacity of 50 rounds.
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>