<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_type56">
		<text>Type 56</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type56_descr">
		<text>The Type 56 rifle is a Chinese-made selective-fire military rifle, developed in the late 1950s as a derivative of the Soviet AK-47. Renowned for its robust construction and reliability, the Type 56 features a gas-operated mechanism and is chambered for the 7.62x39mm cartridge. With a distinctive curved magazine, it gained popularity as a standard infantry weapon in numerous conflicts worldwide. Its enduring design and affordability have contributed to its widespread adoption and use by various military, paramilitary, and insurgent groups.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Most scopes for the Dovetail mount system\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-1</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_type56_1">
		<text>Type 56-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type56_1_descr">
		<text>The Type 56-1 rifle, a variant of the original Chinese Type 56, is a compact and specialized firearm developed for close-quarters combat. With a shortened barrel and folding stock, the Type 56-1 offers enhanced maneuverability while retaining the 7.62x39mm chambering and selective-fire capabilities of its predecessor. Originally designed for vehicle crews and special forces, this rifle's compactness and adaptability have made it suitable for urban warfare and tight spaces, solidifying its status as a versatile firearm in various operational contexts.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		<!-- %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Most scopes for the Dovetail mount system\n -->
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-1</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_type56_2">
		<text>Type 56-2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type56_2_descr">
		<text>The Type 56-2 rifle represents a modernized iteration of the iconic Chinese Type 56 rifle, built upon the foundation of its predecessor's design. Integrating contemporary advancements, this firearm features enhanced ergonomics, improved materials, and updated components, offering heightened accuracy, reliability, and user comfort. Retaining the 7.62x39mm caliber and selective-fire capabilities, the Type 56-2 combines the familiarity of the original model with cutting-edge innovations, making it suitable for a range of operational scenarios. Its modernization ensures compatibility with various accessories, optics, and tactical equipment, aligning the rifle with contemporary military and security needs.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Most scopes for the Dovetail mount system\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-1</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_type81">
		<text>Type 81</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type81_descr">
		<text>The Type 81 rifle is a Chinese-designed, gas-operated, selective-fire firearm that emerged in the late 20th century. Chambered for the 7.62x39mm cartridge, the rifle features a distinctive bullpup configuration, where the action and magazine are located behind the trigger group, resulting in a shorter overall length without compromising barrel length. Notable for its unique design and ergonomic benefits, the Type 81 rifle offers improved maneuverability while retaining the firepower of its caliber. Originally developed for the Chinese military, this rifle gained recognition for its adaptability and saw service with various armed forces and paramilitary organizations, showcasing its versatility in diverse operational environments.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Most scopes for the Dovetail mount system\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-1</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_type81_default">
		<text>Type 81 30-rond magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_type81_default_descr">
		<text>Magazine for the Type 81 rifle, it holds 30 rounds of 7.62x39mm ammunition.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_type81_drum">
		<text>Type 81 65-rond drum magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_type81_drum_descr">
		<text>Magazine for the Type 81 rifle, it holds 65 rounds of 7.62x39mm ammunition.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>