<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- Berill-5M Armoured Suits -->
	<string id="army_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Military P1 Combat Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>Standard issue jacket for the new privates in the corps. Found lacking for most situations, but still outclasses all other jackets of its type. May be quite common in the army but a very rare piece of clothing in the zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="army_4_outfit_name">
		<text>Military P2 Service Outfit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_4_outfit_description">
		<text>A protective outfit contracted by government bureaucrats. Typically issued to helicopter pilots, tank drivers, rear-echelon personnel, conscripts and enlisted servicemen. Provides adequate protection from small mutants. Although its overall combat protection is better than most light armors commonly found on other factions, it is by no means spectacular.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_explorer_outfit_name">
		<text>Berill-5N 'Explorer' suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_explorer_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This item comprises military PS5 series body armour with Class IIA beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. Designed for prolonged recon operations, this outfit is standard issue for most Spetsnaz recon forces in the Zone, but requires a high quality respirator to counteract its weaknesses against radiation but fairs decent with anomalies. This suit the alternative to the Berill-5M for those who want a little more environmental protection.\n
		This particular model has been modified up to facilitate scouting tasks in anomalous areas, increasing the protection againsta anomalies, but suffering in the ballistics side.\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!-- Sunrise suits -->
	<string id="stalker_outfit_army_name">
		<text>"Avalanche" Military Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_army_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Issued to recon units and some Spetnaz specialists for transversing across the Zone's expanse. Its comfy interior and a decent environmental protection makes it a fine choice for any Stalker. If they can get their hands on it, that is. The suit is quite rare as it hardly ever reaches the black market due to its rarity, and the fact that any Stalker who gets their lucky hands on it wouldn't want to sell it.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

<!-- SSP-99 -->
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_2_name">
		<text>SSP-99R Ranger suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_2_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. It provides increased body protection from bullet and splinter damage. It is designed for the guards working with scientific expeditions. It provides good protection from radiation and biological anomalies. It is resistant to chemically aggressive environments and other effects dangerous to the body.\n
		This version comes with an unusually high combat defense, though at the expense of enviromental protection. It seems to be a somewhat new model and hasn't been offically issued among the troops. But even so the trial tests results show promising performance.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

<!-- Skat-9 Military Armoured Suits -->
	<string id="military_outfit_2_name">
		<text>Skat-10 ABR suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_outfit_2_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This suit is the successor of the Skat-9 armoured suit. The Skat-10 ABR (Anomolous Battle Ready) suit uses techniques similar to those emplyoted by the X-10 Exosuit while retaining the ability to switch helmets. Provides similar traits to the exosuit but has more customization options and may find itself even better in some situations.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
