<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk47">
		<text>CMMG MK47 MUTANT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk47_descr">
		<text>The CMMG Mk47 Mutant is an American-made semi-automatic rifle chambered in 7.62×39mm caliber, made by CMMG Inc. It can accept all types of Kalashnikov pattern magazines, including steel, polymer and drum magazines. In 2015, CMMG released its first production Mk47s to stores throughout the US. According to CMMG Production Manager Tyson Bradshaw, he mentioned that CMMG made the rifle due to the need of "consumers to have a reliable, U.S.-made rifle that could properly handle the dimensions of the 7.62x39 mm cartridge. To do this properly, it required CMMG to build the rifle around the caliber. Using AK magazines was decided because they are the most reliable magazines. The Mk47 Mutant has an AR-10-sized bolt carrier, which was enlarged, with a CMMG RKM KeyMod handguard and an upper/lower receiver manufactured from 7075-T6 billet aluminum. The rifle has an AR-15-based pistol grip, safety selector, trigger group and a buffer tube. It was influenced by the CMMG Mk3 assault rifles. The Mk47 relies on a direct impingement gas system.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Most optics for the Picatinny/weaver system.\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO Suppressor multicaliber compatible.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp155">
		<text>MP-155</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp155_descr">
		<text>The Baikal MP-155 is a semiautomatic shotgun that comes in 12 gauge, with 750 mm barrel smooth bore. In production since 2011 an is the most popular model for russian hunters.\n
		The version smuggled to the Zone came modified in factory with the 8 round magazine.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Most optics for the Picatinny/weaver system.\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO Suppressor multicaliber compatible</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16">
		<text>RPK-16</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16_descr">
		<text>The RPK-16 light machine gun is a response to the "Tokar-2" program where it competed against Degtyaryov's submission. In 2018, the Ministry of Defence of the Russian Federation have signed a contract concerning the procurement of the RPK-16, and is expected to take over the role of the RPK-74 in the Russian Armed Forces.\n
		The RPK-16 is chambered in 5.45?39mm which features the traditional Kalashnikov gas-operated long-stroke piston system, and shares several novel technical and ergonomic features derived from the AK-12 program. Such as a Picatinny rail on the top of the receiver for mounting various optical sights and on the bottom of the handguard to mount the Picatinny rail mounted detachable bipod instead of the fixed bipod of the RPK-74, an ergonomic pistol grip and a folding buttstock, and two main barrel lengths; a 550 mm (21.7 in) long barrel (when it is applied or configured for the light machine gun role) and a 370 mm (14.6 in) short barrel (when it is applied or configured for the assault rifle role).\n
		Its design enables it to have an interchangeable barrels that can easily be removed, and the ability to quickly attach a detachable suppressor. It has a combat weight of 6 kg (13.23 lb), a full-length of 1,076 mm (42.4 in), a cyclic rate of fire of 700 rounds per minute, an accuracy range of 800 m (870 yd).\n
		It primarily uses a 95-round drum magazine and is backwards compatible with box magazines from the AK-74, AK-12 and RPK-74.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>