<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_helm_exo_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The Exohelm, named due to its common appearance alongside exoskeleton armors, is a thick steel helmet produced in the same Ukrainian factories as the exoskeleton armors. The accompanying gas mask is a British SF10, which is easily found on the surplus markets after they were replaced for the General Service Respirator (GSR). Though the gas mask is somewhat dated, the heavy steel helmet provides good protection from shrapnel and small-caliber rounds.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_protective_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A high quality curtain helmet made by the same Defense Research Institute as the SSP-99 and SEVA bodysuits, and intended to be used along with both as standard. Has a hermetic design, and allows for complete isolation from the conditions of an anomalous environment. A closed-cycle air filtering system supplies the wearer with consistently cool, clean air, making it more comfortable than typical gas masks.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="wastelander_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. This particular outfit is unusually light compared to average Stalker suits, but possesses a spacious Class IIIA vest and lightweight inserts. It's essentially a more nimble Stalker-made Berill-5M suit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A 'Sunrise' Stalker suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Monolith suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Monolith suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2t suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A CS-2b stalker suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Load-bearing 'Twilight' tactical suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Mercenary 'Twilight' suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Sentinel of Freedom suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-Mt suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A PS5-M suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its anomaly protection is both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Load-bearing 'Sunset' tactical suit </text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A 'Sunset' bandit suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This suit was designed and produced by one of Kiev's defence research institutes and represents an excellent alternative to hand-made stalker suits. It combines a CBRN jumpsuit with a specially-treated class II kevlar vest. Due to the quality materials used, this bodysuit sports good durability within ambient anomalous fields. Still, it is expensive, and not as effective as more modern armor or CBRN systems.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Produced by Freedom craftsmen especially for observing anomalous phenomena in the Zone. The specially-treated materials provide good protection and suit durability during prolongued exploration of anomalous fields. However, the built-in "Sentinel" body armour is ineffective at stopping medium to high-power cartridges.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The Monolith scientific suit includes a flak vest of unknown origin and also features unique modifications for greater resistance to radiation at the cost of being more vulnerable to psy-fields. The anomaly protection and suit durability otherwise match the standard SEVA bodysuit. Curiously, according to some legends, these suits are most often worn by the soldiers who defend the Brain Scorcher in Radar, although no one outside the Monolith faction can easily confirm.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_name">
		<text>CS-4a Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An unofficial version of the SEVA scientific suit that has been extensively improved by Novikov, Clear Sky's resident technician. Aside from having great protection and durability within anomaly fields, it's also extremely comfortable to move around in. These qualities have made it a high-demand suit among Clear Sky and other factions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Bandits have never been terribly interested in the science and research of anomalous fields, but, nevertheless, they use protective suits such as these to organise ambushes and attacks on stalkers where they are not expected at all: in anomalous fields and radiation pockets. The suit has an external insulation coating, which provides good protection against all kinds of anomalous effects. Due to a lack of any protection from physical impacts, the suit is ideally used to ambush unsuspecting victims.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Originally commissioned by the first iteration of UNISG from one of Kiev's defence research institutes for research in the Zone. The special treatment materials provide enhanced protection and durability against radiation and anomalous effects. However, the built-in body armour is easily defeated by most bullet types.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A variant of the SEVA bodysuit that was commissioned by Mercenaries. Used by veteran Mercs on artefact-hunting contracts, this suit provides good anomaly protection for a SEVA. However, it lacks some of the more recent anti-psy-field upgrades.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]As a token of goodwill (and to help cover their research costs), Clear Sky occasionally makes coveted "Pathfinder" suits on commission for use among the Zone's Mercenaries. Compared to the stock SEVA suit, this model is superior across the board. Compared to the original CS-4a Pathfinder, this suit sacrifices protection against chemical anomalies and radiation in exchange for a Class IIIA ballistic vest.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The Duty faction version of the standard SEVA suit. Like the standard suit variant, it consists of a durable anomaly-resistant CBRN jumpsuit and a specially-treated Class II kevlar vest. A solid suit for extended dives into anomaly fields. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md light scientific suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A lighter variant of the Duty scientific suit that has shed almost half its weight at the cost of slightly decreased protection. The ballistic armor has been replaced by a class IIA vest with numerous pockets.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md light Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]As a token of goodwill (and to help cover their research costs), Clear Sky occasionally makes coveted "Pathfinder" suits on commission for use among the Duty faction. Altered according to Duty's needs, this suit has a few differences compared to the CS-4a pathfinder. Namely, its weight has been reduced by almost half at the expense of some of its protection. Despite this, it's an excellent and comfortable outfit for Duty's more curious members.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_name">
		<text>Patchwork anomaly suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A SEVA-like suit made virtually from scratch by one of the Bandits' gifted craftsmen. Compared to the looted SEVAs that are brought in and restored, this patchwork outfit boasts average protection against anomalies while retaining a surprisingly low weight. Additionally, it's rather stylish and comfy, which has allowed it to become a hit among the smooth criminals who can afford it.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This comfortable bodysuit, originally intended for research in the Zone, makes for a great alternative to the various Light Combat or hand-made suits one might have access to. Compared to a standard SEVA suit, it provides improved protection against thermal hazards and blunt trauma. However, its other protective qualities are inferior to the original SEVA.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A variant of the SEVA bodysuit that was commissioned by Mercenaries. Some of its environmental protection systems were stripped down to accommodate Class IIIA plates. Used by veteran mercenaries who are expected to guide researchers and artefact hunters in the more dangerous parts of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A SEVA-like suit made virtually from scratch by an unknown craftsman. Compared to an ordinary Monolith scientific suit, this outfit is lighter and provides better protection from both chemical burns and radiation. However, its other qualities have suffered. It is unknown what role this suit fills within the Monolith faction as a whole, although it's been speculated that it's purpose is largely ceremonial.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ace_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]One of the most technologically advanced bodysuits in the Zone. The ACE armor system incorporates a next-generation CBRN and a pocketed kevlar vest with Class III plate inserts. Using state of the art materials such as selectively-permeable coatings, this suit manages both maximal anomaly protection and wearer comfort. The suit is only used by the most wealthy and explorative Mercenaries, due to the comparatively low ballistic protection provided at its price point.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_name">
		<text>SSP-99 bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone conditions. It is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The suit itself is thermally and electrically resistant and provides good protection from radiation and biological anomalies. Its design is specifically tailored for maximum durability in thermal, chemical, and electrical fields. However, it provides neither bullet nor splinter protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_name">
		<text>SSP-99M bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. It provides improved protection from biological anomalies compared to the SSP-99.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone conditions. It is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the accompanying SSP-99 helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The Diamond variant gives superior protection from electricity.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The Sapphire model provides excellent protection against short-range psi-emissions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The ‘Ruby’ model provides improved protection against melee attacks, and includes an integrated wound healing system.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone conditions. It is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the accompanying SSP-99 helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The Topaz variant provides increased protection from radiation.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids on enemy STALKERs.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Only the most respected members of Freedom will ever be found wearing a suit like this, and even then only when attacking enemy personnel.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies requiring top of the line ballistic protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This makes it a wonderful suit for conducting raids on other STALKERs. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favourite among the Zone's most powerful outlaws.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. A favourite among the Monolith's battle preachers and tactical masters, who claim the confines of the suit to be as comforting as the Sarcophagus itself.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Considered too cumbersome by the Ukrainian government, these suits are never issued to any unit or individual. Thus soldiers - most often Military stalkers and the occasional old veterans - must always find and pay for it through their own means.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. These outfits are smuggled in from Ukrainian factories near the borders of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. A rare sight, since most ISG operatives prefer increased mobility over raw protective power.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This model includes an early-generation CBRN jumpsuit lined with kevlar.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN jumpsuit lined with kevlar and an additional attachment slot.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Venator battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This particular variant is typically found in the hands of elite Duty huntsmen, where its greater defense against mutants is utilized.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an older CBRN jumpsuit with kevlar weave and additional steel reinforcement. Typically found with elite Duty members, particularly those conducting short operations in northern reaches of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Old and exceedingly heavy, it's possible that suits like this were used by the Duty faction to raid Pripyat and clash with Freedom back in 2012.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies operating in areas like Limansk or Pripyat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN that, unfortunately, has not been modified for the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an asbestos-weave jumpsuit, which the wearer dons at their own risk.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A stalker bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Wind of Freedom suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A PS5-M universal protection suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A PSZ-9d armoured suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomaly fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The very first iteration of the military exoskeleton was this Skat-9 armoured suit modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton. Compared to a third-generation exoskeleton, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomaly fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>X-18 exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An armour made by either Monolithians or an unknown manufacturer. It has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A set of CS-2b body armour that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>SSP-99M exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A unique armor system composed of an exoskeleton-powered SSP-99M jumpsuit with an anomaly-resistant Class IIA kevlar vest placed on top. The durable exo-frames are capable of providing mechanical support for carrying heavy loads even through anomaly fields, making it ideal for aiding researchers during deep incursions into the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG tactical exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A UN-branded special tactical suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton. Was never mass-produced due to extraordinary cost and some design flaws. Despite this, it is in demand due to its ability to take on the weight of all carried equipment, and therefore small batches are made in underground facilities outside Ukraine. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Excellent high-tech armor. Domestically developed by one of the research institutes, specifically for the Duty faction. That said, this armour is slowly being phased out in favour of cheaper, more practical suits, and the few exosuits in active service tend to be in the hands of Duty's oldest veterans. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Produced by Freedom’s finest artisans. Experimenting with different modifications, after numerous attempts they managed to create a really successful design. While not always the most practical suit to maintain, it is undeniably powerful, and as such is entrusted only to Freedom's finest warriors and guardsmen. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton of western production for equipping Mercenaries and other armed groups. While not always the most practical suit to maintain in the Zone, it simultaneously allows the wearer to be both heavily armed and extremely well armoured, with enough strength to carry weeks worth of supplies. Most often worn as a morale booster and highly protective utility suit by veteran Mercenary captains expected to lead their men through hellish conditions. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High-tech armor, made on the basis of a military exoskeleton. However, study samples have revealed that its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Wearing this suit feels like being buried under the concrete of the Sarcophagus itself - terrifyingly claustrophobic for most stalkers, but eerily comforting for true servants of the Monolith. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]One of a few exoskeletons assembled by the Renegades back in 2011 to help secure their final push into Clear Sky's base. Unfortunately, they were virtually wiped out before their final victory ever came, thanks to the interference of a Mercenary with a trenchcoat and a marksman rifle. Modern Renegades who wear this armour always go into battle like a man possessed, eager to mete vengeance upon their most hated foes. That is to say, almost everyone else.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The official version of the UNISG exoskeleton. Released in limited quantities by special order of the United Nations. While it still possesses many of the design flaws of other exoskeletons, it's nonetheless seen as a great alternative to light command and scout vehicles, which would have great trouble navigating the Zone anyways, and thus is deployed in their stead.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High-tech armor, based on the original experimental military designs. However, as far as anyone can see, its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Wearing this suit creates an unnatural feeling of bliss and calm within the wearer, although whether this sense of security is genuine or not remains to be seen.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nosorog_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced exosuit. Rumoured to have been the brainchild of a now deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Nosorog almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance. Typically only available to a faction's most valuable members, and even then only during exceptionally dangerous missions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced exosuit. Rumoured to have been the brainchild of a now deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Champion of Freedom almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance. Typically only available to a faction's most valuable members, and even then only during exceptionally dangerous missions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>