<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="bandit_extraexolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Bandit Exolight Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_extraexolight_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The looted then reversed engineered "underwear" of an exoskeleton. This outfit provides almost all the protection one can expect from a full exoskeleton, but due to being stripped of its servos and batteries, it provides none of the strength enhancement. On the positive side, this means the suit is now easier to maintain and, unlike a full exoskeleton, does not prevent the wearer from sprinting. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favourite among the Zone's most powerful and pitiless outlaws.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_extraexolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Sin Exolight Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_extraexolight_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The looted "underwear" of an exoskeleton, sometimes mistakenly known as the "Radsuit". This outfit provides almost all the protection one can expect from a full exoskeleton, but due to being stripped of its servos and batteries, it provides none of the strength enhancement. On the positive side, this means the suit is now easier to maintain and, unlike a full exoskeleton, does not prevent the wearer from sprinting. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favourite among the Zone's most powerful and pitiless outlaws.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_extraexolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade Exolight Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_extraexolight_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A gift from the Bandits, this outfit provides almost all the protection one can expect from a full exoskeleton, but due to being stripped of its servos and batteries, it provides none of the strength enhancement. On the positive side, this means the suit is now easier to maintain and, unlike a full exoskeleton, does not prevent the wearer from sprinting. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favourite among the Zone's most powerful and pitiless outlaws.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_extrascientific_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Sin Patchwork Science Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_extrascientific_light_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A looted SEVA-like suit virtually made from scratch by an unknown craftsman. Compared to other scientific suits, this outfit is lighter and provides good chemical protection. Other than that, however, it's outright worse. It is unknown what role this suit fills within the Sin faction as a whole, although it's been speculated that it's purpose is largely ceremonial.</text>
	</string>

    <string id="cs_extraexoseva_outfit_name">
		<text>CS CBSE Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_extraexoseva_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Clear Sky-requested version of the CBSE suit. The Closed-cycle Breathing System Exoskeleton suit is the newest result of the ever-growing demand for exoskeletons and protective outfits designed to withstand the harshest of Zone's environments. Similarly to SEVA and SSP class suits, the wearer is isolated from outside conditions by layers of anomaly-resistant coating and internal air filtration systems. The outmost shell based on heavy exosuit armor provides excellent protection from bullets, explosions and ruptures. The resulting weight is supported by a new generation of exoskeletons, allowing the user to move and run unhindered. The CBSE suit is as rare as expensive, therefore only the wealthiest and well-connected veterans of the Zone can afford to get one. Duty version of the suit provides better protection from mutant attacks.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_extraexoseva_outfit_name">
		<text>Bandit CBSE Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_extraexoseva_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A looted then reversed engineered version of the CBSE suit. The Closed-cycle Breathing System Exoskeleton suit is the newest result of the ever-growing demand for exoskeletons and protective outfits designed to withstand the harshest of Zone's environments. Similarly to SEVA and SSP class suits, the wearer is isolated from outside conditions by layers of anomaly-resistant coating and internal air filtration systems. The outmost shell based on heavy exosuit armor provides excellent protection from bullets, explosions and ruptures. The resulting weight is supported by a new generation of exoskeletons, allowing the user to move and run unhindered. The CBSE suit is as rare as expensive, therefore only the wealthiest and well-connected veterans of the Zone can afford to get one. Duty version of the suit provides better protection from mutant attacks.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_extraexoseva_outfit_name">
		<text>Sin CBSE Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_extraexoseva_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A looted version of the CBSE suit. The Closed-cycle Breathing System Exoskeleton suit is the newest result of the ever-growing demand for exoskeletons and protective outfits designed to withstand the harshest of Zone's environments. Similarly to SEVA and SSP class suits, the wearer is isolated from outside conditions by layers of anomaly-resistant coating and internal air filtration systems. The outmost shell based on heavy exosuit armor provides excellent protection from bullets, explosions and ruptures. The resulting weight is supported by a new generation of exoskeletons, allowing the user to move and run unhindered. The CBSE suit is as rare as expensive, therefore only the wealthiest and well-connected veterans of the Zone can afford to get one. Duty version of the suit provides better protection from mutant attacks.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_extraexoseva_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade CBSE Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_extraexoseva_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A stolen version of the CBSE suit. The Closed-cycle Breathing System Exoskeleton suit is the newest result of the ever-growing demand for exoskeletons and protective outfits designed to withstand the harshest of Zone's environments. Similarly to SEVA and SSP class suits, the wearer is isolated from outside conditions by layers of anomaly-resistant coating and internal air filtration systems. The outmost shell based on heavy exosuit armor provides excellent protection from bullets, explosions and ruptures. The resulting weight is supported by a new generation of exoskeletons, allowing the user to move and run unhindered. The CBSE suit is as rare as expensive, therefore only the wealthiest and well-connected veterans of the Zone can afford to get one. Duty version of the suit provides better protection from mutant attacks.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
