<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_uzi">
		<text>IMI Uzi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_s">
		<text>Uzi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_descr">
		<text>
		The Uzi is an open-bolt, blowback-operated submachine gun designed by Major Uziel "Uzi" Gal in the late 1940s.\n
		It was one of the first weapons to use a telescoping bolt design which allows the magazine to be housed in the pistol grip for a shorter weapon.\n
		Mainly constructed from stamped sheet metal, the Uzi has relatively few moving parts, making it easy to strip for maintenance or repair.\n
		It is used throughout the world as a police and special-forces firearm, and has been manufactured by Israel Military Industries, FN Herstal, and other manufacturers.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
        %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_mini">
		<text>IMI Mini Uzi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_mini_s">
		<text>Mini Uzi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_mini_descr">
		<text>
		The Mini Uzi is an open-bolt, blowback-operated submachine gun first introduced in 1980.\n
		It is a compact version of the famous Uzi which, despite its small size, retains the robustness and reliability of the original.\n
		Featuring reduced barrel length and a slightly modified mechanism, the Mini Uzi has a greater automatic rate of fire due to the shorter bolt.\n
		This version is particularly popular for operations in urban environments and confined spaces.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
        %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_micro">
		<text>IMI Micro Uzi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_micro_s">
		<text>Micro Uzi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_uzi_micro_descr">
		<text>
		The Micro Uzi is an closed-bolt, blowback-operated submachine gun first introduced in 1986.\n
		It is an extremely scaled down version of the Uzi with a similar stock model as the Mini Uzi.\n
		Featuring reduced barrel length, shorter bolt and increased cyclic rate, the Micro Uzi fires from a closed bolt to improve single-shot accuracy.\n
		It has seen use in several armed forces and ultimately surpassed by the Uzi Pro in 2010.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]ATTACHMENTS:\n
        %c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9x19 compatible suppressor\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_mag_uzi_9x19">
		<text>20-round 9x19 Uzi Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_9x19_s">
		<text>Uzi 20-rounder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_9x19_descr">
		<text>
		20-round magazine for the Uzi family of submachine guns. Standard for the Mini and Micro versions.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_9x19_extended">
		<text>32-round 9x19 Uzi Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_9x19_extended_s">
		<text>Uzi 32-rounder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_9x19_extended_descr">
		<text>
		32-round extended magazine for the Uzi family of submachine guns. Standard for the classic version.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_11.43x23">
		<text>12-round .45 ACP Uzi Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_11.43x23_s">
		<text>Uzi 12-rounder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_11.43x23_descr">
		<text>
		12-round magazine for the Uzi family of submachine guns. Modified to take .45 ACP rounds.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_11.43x23_extended">
		<text>16-round .45 ACP Uzi Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_11.43x23_extended_s">
		<text>Uzi 16-rounder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_uzi_11.43x23_extended_descr">
		<text>
		16-round magazine for the Uzi family of submachine guns. Modified to take .45 ACP rounds.
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_up_uzi_rail_name">
		<text>Scope mount</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_up_uzi_rail_descr">
		<text>
		A rail mount for installing various optics on the Uzi submachine gun.
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>