<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_r">
		<text>M16A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_r_descr">
		<text>The M16A2 assault rifle is a select-fire, magazine-fed firearm that emerged as an evolution of the iconic M16 family. Renowned for its service in the United States military, the M16A2 features a 20-inch barrel, a semi-automatic and three-round burst firing mode, and a detachable magazine capacity of 30 rounds. Distinguished by its ergonomic improvements, such as an adjustable rear sight for varied distances, the M16A2 embodies accuracy and versatility. Adopted during the 1980s, this rifle showcases advancements in design and functionality, reflecting its significance in modern military history.\n\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] "Commando" Upgrade Kit\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] NATO 5.56 suppressor\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_r_commando">
		<text>M16A2 "Commando"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_r_commando_descr">
		<text>The "Commando" variant of the M16A2 assault rifle is a specialized iteration renowned for its enhanced versatility and firepower. Building upon the M16A2's foundation, the Commando model integrates a 20-inch barrel with an M203 underbarrel grenade launcher, allowing operators to engage both individual targets and fortified positions with precision. This select-fire firearm retains the ergonomic advancements of the M16A2, including its adjustable rear sight for diverse engagement ranges, while the integrated M203 grenade launcher extends its combat capabilities. A detachable magazine, with a capacity of 30 rounds, further emphasizes its adaptability on the battlefield. The Commando variant stands as a testament to innovative design, catering to the multifaceted demands of modern warfare.\n\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] NATO 5.56 suppressor\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_commando">
		<text>"Commando" Upgrade Kit for the M16A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_commando_descr">
		<text>The Commando Upgrade kit adds a M203 Grenade Launcher to the rifle, as well as different visuals that displays that it's battle worn and tested.\n\n</text>
	</string>

</string_table>