<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_m14">
		<text>M14</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m14_descr">
		<text>The M14 is an American selective fire battle rifle chambered for the 7.62x51mm round, successor of the venerable M1 Garand. During the last days of the Second World War, the M14 was made as an experimental weapon to address any issues the M1 Garand had, in which case it succeeded by a margin and became the standard-issue rifle of the United States armed forces from 1959 to 1964, where it got replaced by the M16. While somewhat outdated, the M14 still offers good sharpshooter accuracy and damage, making it useful against anything and anybody you may face in the Zone. This M14 comes with a 20-round magazine, quite common in the Zone.\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m21">
		<text>M21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m21_descr">
		<text>The M21 Sniper Weapon System, known as the XM21 before the Vietnam War, is a variant of the M14 meant to be used as a sniper rifle during said war. It has the selector lever locked in the Semi-Automatic position, so it is not capable of auto-fire unlike the M14 itself, while also having a National Match quality barrel, which improves its accuracy. Its most significant difference though would be the 3-9x variable power telescopic sight, the AR TEL scope, already attached with this model. It's an uncommon weapon, somewhat comparable to an SVD.\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mk14new">
		<text>Mk 14 EBR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk14new_descr">
		<text>The Mk 14 Mod 1 is a modernized variant developed for the US Navy SEALs, and thus uses the Navy "Mark" classification. It consists of an M14 inside a Sage EBR chassis, which was developed for the project, with a shortened 18 inch barrel, said barrel increases handling but also reduces accuracy and bullet speed, making it better fit for close-quarters. It's also equipped with Magpul CTR stock on an M4-style buffer tube adapter.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, C-more Railway Tactical, EOTech scopes\n</text>
	</string>

</string_table>