<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_300_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3 Commando - .300 Blackout</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_300_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - Army Universal Rifle) is an Austrian 5.56x45mm NATO bullpup assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr-Daimler-Puch and now manufactured by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG. The Steyr AUG A3 differs from the base model in the presence of four Picatinny slats: the top one is used for attaching sights, a grenade launcher or a vertical front handle can be attached to the bottom, and a laser pointer or other necessary additional equipment is attached to the side.\n
		This is a modification based on the AUG A3 M2 variant, chambered for .300 AAC Blackout.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Trijicon Acog (x4) and PEQ LA5 LAM.\n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_300">
		<text>Ruger SR-556 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_300_descr">
		<text>The SR-556 is a semi-automatic AR-15 style rifle manufactured by Sturm, Ruger & Co. The rifle was introduced in 2009 in .223 Remington/5.56?45mm NATO and as a .308 Winchester AR-10 variant in 2013, the SR-762. It is one of several AR-15 rifles to use a gas piston operation. Ruger announced on May 15, 2009 on the SR-556 being produced, and in January 2016, Ruger discontinued all existing SR-556 rifles in preparation for a new takedown variant.\n
		Several of these rifles came to the Zone through the scientists. According to rumors, six small containers with these guns were sent from foreign sponsors to Professor Sakharov, but 5 of them were lost before arrival.\n
		This weapon has been converted to use .300 AAC Blackout ammunition, reducing its range in exchange of firepower.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for Picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_sc_tac">
		<text>SCAR-SC CQB .300 (BaS)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_sc_tac_descr">
		<text>The SCAR-SC is a subcompact carbine available in 5.56Г—45mm NATO and .300 Blackout, presented in mid-2018. It weighs 3.1 kg, has a 7.5 in (190mm) inch barrel, an overall length of 25.7 in (650mm) and a length of 21.1 in (540mm) collapsed and has a pistol grip with no finger rest. It has a lower effective range of 200m.\n
		This is the SCAR-SC .300 model, chambered for .300 Blackout.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for Picatinny/weaver, B.E. MEYERS MAWL-C1 tactical green laser aim module (included)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: NATO suppressor</text>
	</string>

</string_table>