<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine">
		<text>M1 Carbine - 5.56x45mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_s">
		<text>M1 Carbine 5.56</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_descr">
		<text>M1 Carbine (Карабин M1) - полуавтоматическая винтовка под калибр .30 Carbine, который в метрической системе равен 7,62x33 мм, с магазином на 15 патронов. Он был выпущен в 1942 году и состоял на вооружении вплоть до 1973 года. Однако, несмотря на то, что в 1973 году его производство было прекращено, в мире до сих пор имеется большое количество таких карабинов, в основном для военизированных группировкок. Легкое, короткоствольное и легко управляемое оружие, любой, включая новичка, может легко использовать это оружие долгое время. </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_3006">
		<text>M1 Carbine - .30-06 Springfield</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_3006_s">
		<text>M1 Carbine .30-06</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1carbine_3006_descr">
		<text>The M1 Carbine is a semi-automatic Carbine rifle chambered in .30 Carbine cartridge, which in metrics is 7.62x33mm, with 15 rounds in the magazine. It was manufactured in 1942 and has been in service for years, until 1973. However, despite its end in 1973, a lot of these are still available over the world, mostly for paramilitary forces and the like. A lightweight, short-barrelled and easily manoeuvrable weapon, anyone including rookies can easily use this weapon and keep it for a long time.\n
		This particular weapon is chambered in .30-06 Springfield round (7.62x63mm), the standard cartridge when the weapon was in service in WW2.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Gunsmith modification kit</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1">
		<text>M1A1 "Paratrooper" - 5.56x45mm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_s">
		<text>M1A1 Paratrooper 5.56</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_descr">
		<text>M1A1 - это вариант карабина M1 Carbine (Карабин M1), созданный специально по заказу воздушно-десантных войск. Единственное его отличие - замена полноразмерного приклада на складной, отсутствие ушка штыкового ножа и наличие прицела с двумя диоптриями вместо стандартого регулируемого прицела. Столь же эффективен, как и карабин M1, но имеет немного меньший вес и лучшую управляемость.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_3006">
		<text>M1A1 "Paratrooper" - .30-06 Springfield</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_3006_s">
		<text>M1A1 Paratrooper .30-06</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m1a1_3006_descr">
		<text>The M1A1 is a variant of the M1 Carbine, specifically made by request of Airborne Troopers. Its only difference is the replacement of the solid stock with a folding one, as well as having no bayonet lug and the rearsight having two diopters instead of being adjustable. Just as effective as the M1 Carbine itself, but having slightly lower weight and better handling.\n
		This particular weapon is chambered in .30-06 Springfield round (7.62x63mm), the standard cartridge when the weapon was in service in WW2.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBLE MOD KITS:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Default: Gunsmith modification kit</text>
	</string>

</string_table>