<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_new">
		<text>M4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk18">
		<text>MK18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_ras">
		<text>M4A1 RAS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_ext">
		<text>M4A1 Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a3">
		<text>M16A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a3_descr">
		<text>The M16 is the U.S. military designation for a family of rifles derived from the ArmaLite AR-15 and further developed by Colt starting in the 1960s. The M16 rifle family including the M16/A1/A2/A3/A4 has been the primary infantry rifle of the United States military since the 1960s. With its variants, it has been in use by 15 NATO countries, and is the most produced firearm in its calibre. The M16 is a lightweight, 5.56x45mm calibre, air cooled, gas operated, magazine fed assault rifle, with a rotating bolt, actuated by direct impingement gas operation. The rifle is made of steel, aluminium, and composite plastics.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher (after modification)\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_descr_new">
		<text>Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the M4A1 carbine is a fully automatic variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. In military use, it has largely replaced the submachine guns firing pistol cartridges that are inadequate against modern body armour. The M4A1 is a modified variant of the M4 carbine able to fire automatic or semi-automatic.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher (after modification)\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_custom_descr">
		<text>Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the M4A1 carbine is a fully automatic variant of the M16A2 assault rifle. In military use, it has largely replaced the submachine guns firing pistol cartridges that are inadequate against modern body armour. The M4A1 is a modified variant of the M4 carbine able to fire automatic or semi-automatic.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk18_descr">
		<text>Ideal for CQC (Close Quarters Combat), the MK18 carbine is a specialized variant derived from the M4A1 platform, designed for compactness and maneuverability in urban environments. In military applications, it serves as a replacement for submachine guns firing pistol cartridges, which are deemed ineffective against modern body armor. The MK18 features modifications tailored for close-quarters engagements, offering both automatic and semi-automatic firing capabilities.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] ACOG, Barska ES AC10632, EOTech scopes\n \n</text>
	</string>
</string_table>