<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_guns_groza">
		<text>OTs-14-4A Groza</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_guns_groza_s">
		<text>Groza 4A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_guns_descr">
		<text>The OTs-14-4A "Groza-4" ('Storm') is a Russian selective fire bullpup assault rifle with a grenade launcher, chambered for the 9Ч39mm subsonic cartridge. The OTs-14 Groza line was developed in the 1990s at the Central Design and Research Bureau of Sporting and Hunting Arms. It saw limited use in the Second Chechen War and Russo-Georgian War, and later by Russian police.\n
		Highly valued by the military and stalkers due to its ability to reliably hit both armored and sheltered enemies. It can be assembled in 4 different configurations, depending on the combat mission.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] scope PO4х34\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 under-barrel grenade launcher\n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_groza_guns_nimble">
		<text>OTs-14-4A Groza Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_guns_nimble">
		<text>Groza 2A Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_guns_nimble_descr">
		<text>A copy of the experimental OTs-14-2A rifle, modified by Duty technicians for one of their former high rank members named Danya. This model is chambered for 5.45x39mm, more common than the 9x39mm caliber, and includes a set of extended magazines for 60 rounds, a laser pointer module, and a forward grip, though this last one preempts the use of a grenade launcher.\n
		The former owner asked Petrenko that, if he had to find a new owner for it, it should only be the most worthy member of Duty.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] scope PO4х34, Night Sight PN-23, ELCAN SpecterDR, Acog, Barsca AC10632, Cobra 8-18, Aimpoint PRO, March Tactical 3-24x42 FFP, OKP-7, AimpointMicro, Aimpoint, C-More, Aimpoint CompM4s, Docter, Deltapoint Pro, Eotech, Eotech 553, Kemper, Meprolight, Rakurs, RMR\n</text>
	</string>
</string_table>