<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_lewd">
		<text>Sturmgewehr 44 (StG 44)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_stg44_lewd_descr">
		<text>The StG 44 (short for Sturmgewehr 44, "assault rifle 44") is a German assault rifle developed during World War II by Hugo Schmeisser. Also known by its early designations as the MP 43 and MP 44 (Maschinenpistole 43 and 44). It was an improvement of an earlier design, the Maschinenkarabiner 42(H), and it influenced modern assault rifles, starting by the Soviet AK-47 two years after the end of World War II.\n
		The StG 44 was the first successful assault rifle, with featuring an intermediate cartridge (7.92?33mm Kurz), controllable automatic fire, a more compact design than a battle rifle with a higher rate of fire, and being designed primarily for hitting targets within a few hundred metres. Other rifles at the time were designed to hit targets of over a thousand meters, but this was found to be in excess of the range in which most enemy engagements actually took place.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Sight: Hensdolt & Soehne x4 (ZF39)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: L26 Silencer</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_zf39">
		<text>Hensoldt & Soehne x4 (ZF39)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_zf39_descr">
		<text>In 1939 the Oberkommando of the Wehrmacht (Armed Forces High Command) initiated a directive to start a sniper program. The Zf.39 Turret mount was the result of it. It was mainly used on the Kar98 but the general concept of putting magnifying scopes on rifles was established and so saw also some limited use on other rifles such as the STG44.\n
		Hensoldt & Soehne made the 4x magnification optic on this specific model, other glass manufactures were Zeiss, Kahles, Ajack and Schneider. The reticle is a standard german Post with a single pointed large centroal post and a pair of horizontal stadia lines.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_wpn_sil_l26">
		<text>L26 Silencer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_wpn_sil_l26_descr">
		<text>Patented in Germany as System Schaetzle, the L26 was a departure from the copies of the Russian wipe-based silencer designs. The L26 used a set of six identical cone-shaped metal baffles inside a simple tube. It attached to a rifle by clamping around the front sight, just like the rifle grenade launcher developed for the K98k.\n
		The basic design was used for several different models; basically everything in the Wehrmacht arsenal that was 8mm in diameter (although not the antitank rifle...). It was also made for the MG42, and about 200 of them were actually fielded with MG42's.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_fmj">
		<text>8x33 FNM FMJ BT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_fmj_descr">
		<text>An 8x33mm (7.92x33 Kurz) cartridge with an 8 gram full-metal-jacketed boat-tailed bullet with a lead core in a copper jacket and a brass case, produced by Fabrica Nacional de Municoes de Armas Ligeiras. This is a modern adaptaion of the Mauser Kurz cartridge and offers much greater accuracy than standard Wehrmacht rounds. It is able to penetrate basic ballistic protections, but it also has a moderate chance of bouncing off surfaces.</text>
	</string>
<!-- 	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_fmj_s">
		<text>8x33 FNM FMJ BT</text>
	</string> -->

	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_p43me">
		<text>7.92x33 Kurzpatrone 43 m.E.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_p43me_descr">
		<text>A 7.92x33mm Kurzpatrone 43 mit Eisenkern (Short Cartridge 1943 with Iron Core) cartridge with an 8.1 gram iron-core bullet with a lead layout and a bimetallic jacket in a steel case. 7.9 Kurz was the first mass-produced intermediate cartridge in the world and was achieved through shortening the standard 7.92x57mm Mauser round. It was made specially for Mkb 42 and Stg 44 assault rifles and saw great success despite its limited use. It is able to pierce through basic ballistic body protections as well as some intermediate models in addition to providing a significant stopping power effect, however, it has a high bounce probability off various surfaces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_p43me_s">
		<text>7.92x33 43 m.E.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_sp">
		<text>7.92x33 Kurzpatrone SP</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_sp_descr">
		<text>A modern civillian adaptation of the 7.9 Kurz ammunition. The 7.92x33mm SP was designed as an expanding cartridge purposed for hunting and sport shooting. Features a soft-point projectile in a brass case. It deals much greater damage than standard 7.9x33, but its ballistic performance has worsened drastically.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_sp_s">
		<text>7.92x33 SP</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_p43mh">
		<text>7.92x33 Kurzpatrone 43 m.H.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_p43mh_descr">
		<text>A 7.92x33mm Kurzpatrone 43 mit Hartkern (Short Cartridge 1943 with Hard Core) cartridge with an 8 gram bullet with a tungsten core in a lead layout and a bimetallic jacket in a steel case. An armor-piercing variant of 7.9 Kurz, it was produced in very limited amounts for german assault troops during the last years of WW2. It is able to pierce through basic and intermediate ballistic body protections in addition to providing a significant stopping power effect, however, it has a high bounce probability off various surfaces.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.92x33_lewd_p43mh_s">
		<text>7.92x33 43 m.H.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_stg44_7.925x33">
		<text>StG44 Magazine (7.92x33K)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stg44_7.925x33_descr">
		<text>The magazine for the StG44 in 7.92x33 Kurzpatrone holds 30 rounds.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>