<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n24">
		<text>5.45x39mm 7N24 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n24_desc">
		<text>This variant of 5.45x39mm, indexed by GRAU as 7N24, provides better armor piercing capabilities than the other AP variants of 5.45x39mm in the Zone. It is not as popular as 7N22, due to the relative rarity and price of this ammunition. However, stalkers report these rounds being far more reliable out in the field at penetrating armor at distance.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n24_bad">
		<text>5.45x39mm 7N24 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n24_bad_desc">
		<text>This variant of 5.45x39mm, indexed by GRAU as 7N24, provides better armor piercing capabilities than the other AP variants of 5.45x39mm in the Zone. It is not as popular as 7N22, due to the relative rarity and price of this ammunition. However, stalkers report these rounds being far more reliable out in the field at penetrating armor at distance. This box in particular seems like it was exposed to water, so misfires with these rounds may occur.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n39">
		<text>5.45x39mm 7N39 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n39_desc">
		<text>The most modern variant of 5.45x39mm available, the 7N39 was developed as part of Russia's Ratnik program. It found its way into the Zone through similar means as the AK-12 series of rifles. Being very new and only issued to Russian Spetsnaz troops, only very few traders might have these for sale and because of its' inherent value, is usually a huge luxury in the Zone. The most veteran of stalkers who get to use this ammunition report great effectiveness even against exoskeletons.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IV\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n39_bad">
		<text>5.45x39mm 7N39 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n39_bad_desc">
		<text>The most modern variant of 5.45x39mm available, the 7N39 was developed as part of Russia's Ratnik program. It found its way into the Zone through similar means as the AK-12 series of rifles. Being very new and only issued to Russian Spetsnaz troops, only very few traders might have these for sale and because of its' inherent value, is usually a huge luxury in the Zone. The most veteran of stalkers who get to use this ammunition report great effectiveness even against exoskeletons. This exact box looks like its been exposed to the elements and while it will probably retain how effective it is, it will cause malfunctions and wear on the gun, if used.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IV\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_7n23">
		<text>7.62x39mm 7N23 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_7n23_desc">
		<text>A huge upgrade from the Chinese armor-piercing rounds commonly found in the Zone, the 7N23 was adopted for service back in 2003. It has since proven its' effectiveness in the field and while not being as common, it is nonetheless very sought after by stalkers because of its great armor-piercing capabilities. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_7n23_bad">
		<text>7.62x39mm 7N23 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_7n23_bad_desc">
		<text>A huge upgrade from the Chinese armor-piercing rounds commonly found in the Zone, the 7N23 was adopted for service back in 2003. It has since proven its' effectiveness in the field and while not being as common, it is nonetheless very sought after by stalkers because of its great armor-piercing capabilities. This box in particular seems like it has been exposed to the elements for prolonged periods of time due to the corrosion seen on some of the cartridges.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_bz">
		<text>7.62x39mm 57-BZ-231 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_bz_desc">
		<text>These 57-BZ-231 rounds are better known as "BZ" among soldiers. These are an armor piercing incendiary variant of the old 7.62x39mm PS variant. The cartridge has a tendency to not ignite upon impact, however, making its incendiary effect slightly inconsistent, but the heightened temperature upon impact in combination with the strengthened core give the round very great effectiveness even against exoskeletons found in the Zone. Because of this, these rounds are very handy in the hands of anyone fighting better equipped individuals in the Zone. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IV\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high due to the incendiary properties</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_bz_bad">
		<text>7.62x39mm 57-BZ-231 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_bz_bad_desc">
		<text>These 57-BZ-231 rounds are better known as "BZ" among soldiers. These are an armor piercing incendiary variant of the old 7.62x39mm PS variant. The cartridge has a tendency to not ignite upon impact, however, making its incendiary effect slightly inconsistent, but the heightened temperature upon impact in combination with the strengthened core give the round very great effectiveness even against exoskeletons found in the Zone. Because of this, these rounds are very handy in the hands of anyone fighting better equipped individuals in the Zone. This box specifically has been not given proper care and some of the cartridges are no longer suitable for use.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IV\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high due to the incendiary properties</text>
	</string>
	

	<string id="st_ammo_9x18_7n25">
		<text>9x18mm 7N25 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x18_7n25_desc">
		<text>An imported modern variant of the 9x18mm, the 7N25 is a very potent armor penetrator at close range. It is still manufactured in the Russian Tula Arms plant, therefore the supply is plentiful, although still lower than other variants of this cartridge in the Zone. Despite being more effective  in combat, it still loses to higher calibers. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_9x18_7n25_bad">
		<text>9x18mm 7N25 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x18_7n25_bad_desc">
		<text>An imported modern variant of the 9x18mm, the 7N25 is a very potent armor penetrator at close range. It is still manufactured in the Russian Tula Arms plant, therefore the supply is plentiful, although still lower than other variants of this cartridge in the Zone. Despite being more effective  in combat, it still loses to higher calibers. This box looks like it has been damaged by the elements. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x25_p41">
		<text>7.62x25mm P-41 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x25_p41_desc">
		<text>The P-41 is a very old variant of 7.62x25mm, adopted back in 1941. This cartridge has an armor piercing bullet as well as an incendiary composite inside, ensuring good penetrative capabilities and great damage to unarmored human targets. Stalkers in southern parts of the Zone make use of these to effectively dispatch of bandits. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high due to incendiary properties</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x25_p41_bad">
		<text>7.62x25mm P-41 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x25_p41_bad_desc">
		<text>The P-41 is a very old variant of 7.62x25mm, adopted back in 1941. This cartridge has an armor piercing bullet as well as an incendiary composite inside, ensuring good penetrative capabilities and great damage to unarmored human targets. Stalkers in southern parts of the Zone make use of these to effectively dispatch of bandits. This box looks like it has been exposed to the elements. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high due to incendiary properties</text>
	</string>
	

	<string id="st_ammo_9x19_7n31">
		<text>9x19mm 7N31 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x19_7n31_desc">
		<text>A Russian variant of the common 9x19 cartridge. Many mistake the 7N21 variant present in the Zone for an armor piercing one, however, the 7N31 was in fact developed as the actual armor piercing variant. It is very effective against soft body armor. Due to the pressure and application, it should only be loaded into Russian firearms. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_9x19_7n31_bad">
		<text>9x19mm 7N31 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x19_7n31_bad_desc">
		<text>A Russian variant of the common 9x19 cartridge. Many mistake the 7N21 variant present in the Zone for an armor piercing one, however, the 7N31 was in fact developed as the actual armor piercing variant. It is very effective against soft body armor. Due to the pressure and application, it should only be loaded into Russian firearms. This box looks like it has been exposed to water. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_barnaul">
		<text>7.62x54mmR "Barnaul" rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_barnaul_desc">
		<text>This is a box of civilian-grade 7.62x54mmR ammunition. Unlike military ammo, this ammunition has lower gunpowder loads and is more intended for hunting and sports shooting, rather than combat. Because of this, the ammo is designed to be more stable, ensuring less deviation, lower weapon wear at the expense of it being less effective in combat due to its rather weak, non-penetrating core. This ammo is not very popular in the Zone, however, it is cheaper and easier to obtain than military ammunition, making it a very valid option for less wealthy stalkers.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium - high</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_barnaul_bad">
		<text>7.62x54mmR "Barnaul" rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_barnaul_bad_desc">
		<text>This is a box of civilian-grade 7.62x54mmR ammunition. Unlike military ammo, this ammunition has lower gunpowder loads and is more intended for hunting and sports shooting, rather than combat. Because of this, the ammo is designed to be more stable, ensuring less deviation, lower weapon wear at the expense of it being less effective in combat due to its rather weak, non-penetrating core. This ammo is not very popular in the Zone, however, it is cheaper and easier to obtain than military ammunition, making it a very valid option for less wealthy stalkers. This box looks like it has been damaged by the elements. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IIIA\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium - high</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n26">
		<text>7.62x54mmR 7N26 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n26_desc">
		<text>This variant of 7.62x54mmR was created in the late 90s to fulfill the armor-piercing needs of the Russian army. The cartridge is very effective against armor compared to other variants available in the Zone, although, it is significantly rarer. In demand among factions due to its very good price-quality ratio.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n26_bad">
		<text>7.62x54mmR 7N26 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n26_bad_desc">
		<text>This variant of 7.62x54mmR was created in the late 90s to fulfill the armor-piercing needs of the Russian army. The cartridge is very effective against armor compared to other variants available in the Zone, although, it is significantly rarer. In demand among factions due to its very good price-quality ratio. This box looks like it has been damaged by the elements.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n37">
		<text>7.62x54mmR 7N37 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n37_desc">
		<text>The most modern variant of 7.62x54mmR, 7N37 is an incredibly rare ammo type developed as part of Russia's Ratnik program. The bullet of this variant has a tungsten-cobalt core, making it VERY effective at penetrating armor. It is safe to say that no armor in the Zone can protect the wearer against this cartridge. As a result, this cartridge is extremely valuable and extremely rare.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IV\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n37_bad">
		<text>7.62x54mmR 7N37 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n37_bad_desc">
		<text>The most modern variant of 7.62x54mmR, 7N37 is an incredibly rare ammo type developed as part of Russia's Ratnik program. The bullet of this variant has a tungsten-cobalt core, making it VERY effective at penetrating armor. It is safe to say that no armor in the Zone can protect the wearer against this cartridge. As a result, this cartridge is extremely valuable and extremely rare. This box was not taken proper care of and as a result, was damaged by water.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]IV\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_ammo_pg-7vl">
		<text>PG-7VL warhead</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_pg-7vl_desc">
		<text>An improvement over the other existing warheads in the Zone, the PG-7VL was designed to penetrate armor better. It is heavier than its older variants and doesn't fly as straight or as far, however, it delivers a bigger blast. Beloved by factions for use against vehicles or massive mutant packs.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Blast power: %c[ui_gray_1]high\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Blast radius: %c[ui_gray_1]5.9 m\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Fragments' radius: %c[ui_gray_1]46 m\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Av. number of fragments: %c[ui_gray_1]184 (small shrapnels)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Explosion delay: %c[ui_gray_1]none (explodes on impact)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_pg-7vl_bad">
		<text>PG-7VL warhead (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_pg-7vl_bad_desc">
		<text>An improvement over the other existing warheads in the Zone, the PG-7VL was designed to penetrate armor better. It is heavier than its older variants and doesn't fly as straight or as far, however, it delivers a bigger blast. Beloved by factions for use against vehicles or massive mutant packs. This warhead has signs of corrosion.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Blast power: %c[ui_gray_1]high\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Blast radius: %c[ui_gray_1]5.9 m\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Fragments' radius: %c[ui_gray_1]46 m\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Av. number of fragments: %c[ui_gray_1]184 (small shrapnels)\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Explosion delay: %c[ui_gray_1]none (explodes on impact)</text>
	</string>



	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_7n12">
		<text>9x39mm 7N12 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_7n12_desc">
		<text>The 7N12 is an improved variant of the SP-6 cartridge, intended for more accurate fire and superior armor penetration. Due to its' special purpose, the cartridge is fairly rare and expensive. Requires a suppressor for stealth firing. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_7n12_bad">
		<text>9x39mm 7N12 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_7n12_bad_desc">
		<text>The 7N12 is an improved variant of the SP-6 cartridge, intended for more accurate fire and superior armor penetration. Due to its' special purpose, the cartridge is fairly rare and expensive. Requires a suppressor for stealth firing. This box has been damaged by the elements. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_pab9">
		<text>9x39mm PAB-9 rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_pab9_desc">
		<text>The PAB-9 was an attempt to manufacture a cheaper variant of the SP-6 cartridge. Despite being cheaper to manufacture, the cartridge was deemed a failure because of its tendency to damage the weapon it is fired from. According to various tests with VSS and AS VAL rifles, use of this cartridge reduces barrel life by 3,000 rounds. Despite its relative rarity, it's not in wide demand, therefore it is fairly inexpensive. Requires a suppressor for stealth firing.  \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium - high</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_pab9_bad">
		<text>9x39mm PAB-9 rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_9x39_pab9_bad_desc">
		<text>The PAB-9 was an attempt to manufacture a cheaper variant of the SP-6 cartridge. Despite being cheaper to manufacture, the cartridge was deemed a failure because of its tendency to damage the weapon it is fired from. According to various tests with VSS and AS VAL rifles, use of this cartridge reduces barrel life by 3,000 rounds. Despite its relative rarity, it's not in wide demand, therefore it is fairly inexpensive. Requires a suppressor for stealth firing. This box has been damaged by the elements to the point that use of this cartridge will guarantee weapon failure.  \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium - high</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_ammo_12x70_buck_1">
		<text>12x70 #1 buckshot shells</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_12x70_buck_1_desc">
		<text>This is a box of Russian-imported #1 buckshot shells, manufactured by a small civilian ammunition brand. These shells contain 14 pellets each, smaller in diameter than normal #00 buckshot. Not generally recommended for combat, however these can prove effective against unarmored targets and smaller mutants and that is the reason it is quite common among rookie stalkers and various faction combatants who do not get into combat with enemies. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]none\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] expanding cloud of pellets, short eff. range</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_12x70_buck_1_bad">
		<text>12x70 #1 buckshot shells (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_12x70_buck_1_bad_desc">
		<text>This is a box of Russian-imported #1 buckshot shells, manufactured by a small civilian ammunition brand. These shells contain 14 pellets each, smaller in diameter than normal #00 buckshot. Not generally recommended for combat, however these can prove effective against unarmored targets and smaller mutants and that is the reason it is quite common among rookie stalkers and various faction combatants who do not get into combat with enemies. This box has been exposed to the elements. \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]none\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]high\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] expanding cloud of pellets, short eff. range</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_12.7x55_tp">
		<text>12.7x55mm TP rounds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_12.7x55_tp_desc">
		<text>This is a box of very specialized 12.7x55mm cartridges, designed for use with the ShAK-12 rifle. It is overall a shorter cartridge compared to the STs-130 and therefore, can not be used with a VSSK sniper rifle. These cartridges are not as accurate as STs-130, however, they still deliver a very respectable punch.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium-high</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ammo_12.7x55_tp_bad">
		<text>12.7x55mm TP rounds (old)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ammo_12.7x55_tp_bad_desc">
		<text>This is a box of very specialized 12.7x55mm cartridges, designed for use with the ShAK-12 rifle. It is overall a shorter cartridge compared to the STs-130 and therefore, can not be used with a VSSK sniper rifle. These cartridges are not as accurate as STs-130, however, they still deliver a very respectable punch. This box has been exposed to humidity for prolonged periods.\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Highest pierced armour class: %c[ui_gray_1]III\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Tissue damage rating: %c[ui_gray_1]medium-high</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!--- short ammo names--->
<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n24_s">
	<text>5.45x39 7N24</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n24_bad_s">
	<text>5.45x39 7N24</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n39_s">
	<text>5.45x39 7N39</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_5.45x39_7n39_bad_s">
	<text>5.45x39 7N39</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_7n23_s">
	<text>7.62x39 7N23</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_7n23_bad_s">
	<text>7.62x39 7N23</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_bz_s">
	<text>7.62x39 BZ</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x39_bz_bad_s">
	<text>7.62x39 BZ</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x18_7n25_s">
	<text>9x18 7N25</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x18_7n25_bad_s">
	<text>9x18 7N25</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x25_p41_s">
	<text>7.62x25 P-41</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x25_p41_bad_s">
	<text>7.62x25 P-41</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x19_7n31_s">
	<text>9x19 7N31</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x19_7n31_bad_s">
	<text>9x19 7N31</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_barnaul_s">
	<text>7.62x54R Barnaul</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_barnaul_bad_s">
	<text>7.62x54R Barnaul</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n26_s">
	<text>7.62x54R 7N26</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n26_bad_s">
	<text>7.62x54R 7N26</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n37_s">
	<text>7.62x54R 7N37</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_7.62x54_7n37_bad_s">
	<text>7.62x54R 7N37</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_pg-7vl_s">
	<text>PG-7VL</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_pg-7vl_bad_s">
	<text>PG-7VL</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x39_7n12_s">
	<text>9x39 7N12</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x39_7n12_bad_s">
	<text>9x39 7N12</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x39_pab9_s">
	<text>9x39 PAB-9</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_9x39_pab9_bad_s">
	<text>9x39 PAB-9</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_12x70_buck_1_s">
	<text>12x70 #1 Buck</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_12x70_buck_1_bad_s">
	<text>12x70 #1 Buck</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_12.7x55_tp_s">
	<text>12.7x55 TP</text>
</string>
<string id="st_ammo_12.7x55_tp_bad_s">
	<text>12.7x55 TP</text>
</string>


</string_table>